oh
hello how lucky that i met you in
this deserted place my name
is ines horn
i ask you for help you are my
only hope when working in the swamp
whereby a toad got infected with flu
only a special healing potion can
save me the potion was supposed to arrive yesterday with
a caravan but
bandits ambushed the caravan and
stole the potion if i haven't taken the potion
by tomorrow
then i will die please bring me
the potion i don't want to die yet
i was able to find out that the
bandit camp is behind the next one door
is I would like that but unfortunately
I'm too weak to storm the camp
here on the other hand looks very strong
bandits always hide their
loot inside the camp you
'll probably have
to go there to get the potion
you're right it's that simple it not
the bandits have divided their camp into individual
rooms and for each room
you need a
key the bandits carry the keys with
them for each key you have to
defeat a bandit and take the key
don't even
try to steal the keys from the bandits only in
an open fight he has a chance
why should I lie to you if
If you have a key, you can use it to
open the next door.
A key only fits on
one door. The warehouse begins behind the
door at the end of the corridor.
Here you have the key. In the warehouse
, there are treacherous traps everywhere,
so be careful you have everything so far
understood well
picture bring me the potion so i
don't have to die thank you there
is someone that's football
disappear ap
he is there now it's all going well
hey
your life
yes there's an
intruder coming you'll pay for that
we're bandits sneaking up
as it is bandit resistance is
come here you get out
hey
this is an end
come here you don't get out
yes
hey
chew m
sid on the lever to open the gate
sorry but i followed you secretly
as i see you were
able to defeat the bandits and recover the potion
i knew he could do it
thank you very much you saved my life
i owe you a lot